VINCE CHANG

7120 Shoreline Drive #2214, San Diego, CA 92122 Phone: (650) 274-2333 : Email: vincechangsf@gmail.com

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/vincechang26: Portfolio: https://vincehacks.github.io

OBJECTIVE

I am a UC San Diego new grad with a B.S in Computer Science. I am a unique problem solver who has work experience in leadership, teamwork, and is passionate about motivating others. As a Software Engineer, I would become an asset to a company by bringing innovated ideas and by developing clean deployable code.

EDUCATION

University of California, San Diego, CA, September 2014 - Present

- Computer Science, B.S March 2017 expected graduation
- Relevant Coursework:
 - Software Engineering
 - Advanced Data Structures
- Design & Analysis of Algorithms
- · Operating Systems

WORK EXPERIENCE

Instructional Assistant, UCSD, San Diego, CA, Sept 2016 - Dec 2016 Usability and Information Architecture

- Designed curriculum that emphasized on user interaction, research, and prototyping with design tools
- · Assisted students with building a personal web portfolio in HTML and CSS

Software Engineering Intern, DIRECTV, El Segundo, CA, June 2016 - Sept 2016

- Performed system level functional software testing for NFL Sunday Ticket on various platforms: iOS, Android, Windows, Samsung, Amazon, Google
- · Learned the Django Platform
- · Measured system performance and stress-tested servers
- View what I have accomplished: http://tinyurl.com/zmw7zes

Computer Science Tutor, UCSD, San Diego, CA, March 2015 - June 2016 Software Engineering; Intro to Computer Science: Java; Software Tools Lab

- Assisted students with an introduction to software development and agile engineering methods, including specification, design, implementation, testing
- Assisted students with hands-on experience with designing, editing, compiling, and executing programming constructs
- · Monitored labs that focus on a various topics: vim, unix, GIT, Python

PROJECTS

Shake-Kryptic (WIP)

Web/mobile app that allows users to generate a unique handshake with others. Users are recommended to submit different gestures to create unique handshakes.

Synth

Mobile Music App that has been redesigned through strategically conducted case studies. We evaluated the daily music user's likes/dislikes on Spotify, Pandora, Soundcloud, and Google Play. After analyzing and weighing pros and cons, my team is proud to announce the birth of Synth. http://tinyurl.com/jacw8fr

Dancify (SD HACK-A-THON)

Web app that connects you with other people who would like to attend a dance event. Users are matched based on their profile information which include availability, location, gender preference, and music genre. http://devpost.com/software/dancify

TECH SKILLS

- Agile Methods
- OO Design
- Android
- Hack-a-Thon
- Debugging
- Github
- MVC
- Django /MVC
- UML Diagrams
- SCRUM

LANGUAGES

- Java
- C++
- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- Python (WIP)
- Ruby (WIP)

IDE's

- Android Studio
- Eclipse
- IntelliJ